<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on Lucas Chaufournier</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on Lucas Chaufournier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Work</title>
      <link>/post/how-i-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-i-work/</guid>
      <description> How I Work Current Linux Distribution: Ubuntu Server 18.04
Current Workstation: 15&amp;rdquo; 2016 Macbook Pro w/ 27&amp;rdquo; Monitor
Technical Specs:
 Ram: 16gb Hard Disk: 512gb CPU: Intel i7 2.6GHz Intel Core  Applications:
 Text Editor: Visual Studio Code and Vim for servers Web Browser: Google Chrome Music Player: Spotify Word Processor: Google Docs Note Taking: Paper and Whiteboards Research Notebook: Giving the rocketbook everlast a try for a bit, Paper for everything else To do list: Index Cards, trying to migrate to bullet journal Calendar: Google Calendar  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVM Tips</title>
      <link>/post/kvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kvm/</guid>
      <description>Useful Tips KVM can sometimes be tricky when used on a headless server. To fix it so you can use curses, you need to edit the following things in the vm.
 Modify /etc/default/grub  GRUB_CMDLINE_LINUX_DEFAUL=&amp;quot;fbcon=map:99 text&amp;quot; GRUB_TERMINAL=console  Run update-grub
 Blacklist vga16fb  echo &#39;install vga16fb /bin/true&#39; &amp;gt;/etc/modprobe.d/graphics-disabled.conf  Troubleshooting For networking, it is useful to use a tap device. Make sure the /etc/qemu-ifup script has switch set to the bridge device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LXC: Linux Containers Commands</title>
      <link>/post/lxc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/lxc/</guid>
      <description>Notes:  I use the name c1 in the following commands. Replace c1 with the container you wish to use. To view actual stats of a container you can see:  /sys/fs/cgroup/memory/lxc/c1  replace memory with a cgroup
Installing  Install from the ubuntu package manager
$ sudo apt-get install lxc uidmap cgroup-lite  Check if system is configured properly
$ sudo lxc-checkconfig   Commands  Create a Container  # lxc-create -n c1 -t ubuntu  This creates container c1 from the template ubuntu(replace as you see fit with an available template/usr/share/lxc/templates)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tmux Usage</title>
      <link>/post/tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tmux/</guid>
      <description>Installation  To install tmux, use the provided package manager. Ubuntu is shown below:  $ sudo apt-get install tmux  Commands  Shortcut (Used to invoke all commands for tmux)  ctrl-b command   Show Sessions ctrl-b S or $ tmux ls
 Create a New Session
  $ tmux new -s session_name   Attach to an Existing Session  $ tmux a -t session   Kill a Session  $ tmux kill-session -t session-name  Commands    Command Code Description     ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 09:59:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>I am a fourth year MS/PhD student working in the LASS Lab with Prashant Shenoy at the University of Massachusetts Amherst. My area of focus is in cloud computing, IOT and distributed systems, though my interests cross into many areas across computing. Currently we are evaluating edge clouds and their benefits towards smart cities.
Apart from cloud computing, I enjoy studying how technology can interact with people and the surrounding world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>